Guide to the Philip Agee Papers TAM.517
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series VI, Subject Files
  - Subseries VI-A, Countries: Latin America and the Caribbean
    - "Revolution Beyond Our Borders: Sandinista Intervention in Central America" by Thomas Borge Special Report Issued by the United States Department of State, Jul 19, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - School of the Americas Watch, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - The Other Americas Radio, 1976-1988 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Uruguay, 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - US Intervention in Latin America (Conference in Venezuela), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Venezuela, 1993, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Subseries VI-B, Countries: Other
    - Afghanistan, 1981-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Algeria, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Angola, 1976-1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Australia, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cambodia, 1975, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - China, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Congo, Jun 4, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - East Timor, 1982-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Egypt, 1985-1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Ethiopia, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Europe, Eastern - Post-Communism, Rise of Fascism, 1990-1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Europe, Western, 1975-1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ghana, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - India, Pakistan, Bangladesh, 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Indonesia, 1978-1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Iran, 1978-1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Iraq, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Israel (Includes Relations with Africa), 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Italy (Re-Emergence of Fascism), 1993-1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Japan, 1990-1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Korea, 1977-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Laos, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Libya, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Mauritius, Apr 30, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Mozambique, 1976-1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Namibia, Feb 14, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - New Zealand, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - New Zealand: Big Sister Wellington, Aotearoa, Mar 1987 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - New Zealand Security Intelligence Service, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 27A)
    - New Zealand: Wellington Confidential No. 36, Jun 1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Nigeria, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Norway, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Pakistan, 1985-1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Palestine, 1978, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Philippines, 1969-1990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Portugal, 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Thailand, Dec 1984-Jan 1985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Russia, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Saudi Arabia, May 17, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Singapore, Aug 30, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - South Africa, 1979-1994 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Sudan, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Turkey (Includes Additional Research Material), 1982-1995 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Vietnam, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Zaire, 1981-1997 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Zambia, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Zimbabwe, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Subseries VI-C, Expulsions
    - France: Applications for Permissions to Re-enter the Country, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - France: Clippings (Foreign), 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - France: Correspondence, Statements, 1977-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - France: Treaty with the United States 1959-1960, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Germany: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Germany: Treaty with the United States 1954, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Germany: Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Germany: Agee's Notes and Statements, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Great Britain: Agee/Hosenball Defence Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Great Britain: Agee/Hosenball Defence Committee - Posters, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Great Britain: Agee/Hosenball Deportation: House of Commons, Official Report, Vol. 931, No. 98, May 4, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Great Britain: Campaigns Against Agee's Expulsion, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Nov 16, 1976-Nov 17, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Nov 16, 1976-Nov 17, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Nov 18, 1976-Nov 19, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Nov 18, 1976-Nov 19, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Nov 20, 1976-Nov 25, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Nov 20, 1976-Nov 25, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Nov 26, 1976-Nov 30, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Nov 26, 1976-Nov 30, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Dec 1, 1976-Dec 7, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Dec 1, 1976-Dec 7, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Dec 8, 1976-Dec 31, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Dec 8, 1976-Dec 31, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Jan 1, 1977-Jan 11, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Jan 1, 1977-Jan 11, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Jan 12, 1977-Jan 13, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Jan 12, 1977-Jan 13, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Jan 14, 1977-Jan 17, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Jan 14, 1977-Jan 17, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Jan 18, 1977-Jan 31, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Jan 18, 1977-Jan 31, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Feb 1, 1977-Feb 16, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 32A)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Feb 1, 1977-Feb 16, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Feb 17, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Feb 17, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Feb 18, 1977-Feb 19, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Feb 18, 1977-Feb 19, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Feb 20, 1977-Feb 21, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Feb 20, 1977-Feb 21, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Feb 22, 1977-Feb 23, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Feb 22, 1977-Feb 23, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Feb 24, 1977-Feb 28, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Feb 24, 1977-Feb 28, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Mar 1, 1977-Mar 5, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Mar 1, 1977-Mar 5, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Mar 5, 1977-Mar 21, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Mar 5 1977-Mar 21, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Mar 22, 1977-Mar 31, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Mar 22, 1977-Mar 31, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Apr 1, 1977-Apr 29, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Apr 1, 1977-Apr 29, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, May 1, 1977-Jun 5, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, May 1, 1977-Jun 5, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Great Britain: Clippings - Copies, Aug 1977-Dec 1977, Mar 1994 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Great Britain: Clippings, Aug 1977-Dec 1977, Mar 1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Great Britain: Clippings (Foreign), Jan 1977-Feb 19977 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Great Britain: Correspondence, 1976-1977, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Great Britain: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Great Britain: Correspondence: National Union of Journalists, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Great Britain: Correspondence: PEN-World Association of Writers, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Great Britain: Legal Defence, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Great Britain: Legal Defence 2 (Includes Handwritten Notes), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Great Britain: Correspondence: University of Dundee, Edinburgh, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Great Britain: Manuscripts, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Great Britain: Parliamentary Debates: "Mr. Agee and Mr. Hosenball", 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Great Britain: Petition to the European Human Rights Commission, Dec 1, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Great Britain: Petition to the Government, Dec 1, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Great Britain: Statement by Philip B. F. Agee to the Home Security, Attachments 1-17 (Articles, Interviews, Clippings), 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Great Britain: Statements by Philip B. F. Agee to the Home Security, Attachments 18-29 (Articles, Interviews, Clippings), 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Great Britain: Statement by Philip B. F. Agee to the Home Secretary's Independent Panel in Defence Against Deportation From the United Kingdom, Jan 11, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Great Britain: Statement by Philip B. F. Agee to the Home Secretary's Independent Panel in Defence Against Deportation from the United Kingdom, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Great Britain: Treaty with the United States, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Great Britain: Statement by Philip B. F. Agee to the Home Secretary's Independent Panel in Defence Against Deportation from the United Kingdom (Attachments), Jan 11, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Great Britain: Thank You Letter for the Support of Anti-Deportation Campaign, May 26, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - The Netherlands: Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Netherlands: Correspondence, 1977-1978, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The Netherlands: Governmental Documents, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Netherlands: Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Netherlands: Parliamentary Debate Re: Agee, Feb 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Netherlands: Statements and Appeals by Philip Agee, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - The Netherlands: Treaty with the United States, 1956, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Norway: Refusal of Visa Application, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Subseries VI-D, Individuals, Organizations, Topics
    - Abbie Hoffman Activisit Foundation, Jul 15, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "Abolition of the Central Intelligence Agency" Act Proposed by Senator David Moynihan, Jan 4, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - African-American Labor Center (AALC), 1968-1982 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Aggregate Intelligence Budget Act of 1995, Jan 4, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - The All African People Revolutionary Party, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - "Alleged Assassination Plots Involving Foreign Leaders" - An Interim Report of the Select Committee to Study Governmental Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities, Nov 20, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) - includes "AIFLD: The Trojan Horse - An EPICA Special Report" by Michael J. Sussman, 1974-1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - American University, Cairo, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Ames, Aldrich Hazen: "An Assessment of the Aldrich H. Ames Espionage Case and its Implications for US Intelligence: A Report of the US Senate Select Committee on Intelligence", Nov 1, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Ames, Aldrich Hazen: Clippings, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Ames, Aldrich Hazen: Legal Documents, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Ames, Aldrich Hazen: Report of Senate Select Committee on Intelligence (News Release), Nov 1, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Ames, Aldrich Hazen: Statement Re: Rosario Ames, Apr 28, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Anti-NATO Commission, Madrid, Nov 1986 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - The Asian American Free Labor Institute (AAFLI), Sep 12, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Assassination: Abdul Ghani Lone - Kashmiri Leader, Aug 3, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Assassination Attempt of Pope John Paul II, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Assassinations: John F. and Robert Kennedy, 1968-1983 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Association of National Security Alumni (ANSA), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - The Balkan Archive (Los Angeles, CA), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Bechtel Corporation and the CIA (Clipping), Sep.Oct 1978 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Bibliography From Readers' Guide to Periodical Literature 1967-1984, Requested from the John F. Kennedy Institute, Freie Universitat Berlin by Thomas Poese, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Black Panthers Party, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Booth, Alan R.: History Professor at Ohio University, Syllabi: "Espionage and History" and "The Folklore of Espionage", 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Bresche: Revolutionare Marxistische Liga, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - "British Intelligence and Covert Actions": Book by Jonathan Bloch and Pat Fitzgerald (Introduction by Philip Agee); Clippings and Correspondence, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 40A)
    - Callaghan, Arthur, CIA Station Chief in Iran: Hearing of Telephone Conversation, Jun 11, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - CIA: Clippings, 1971-1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - CIA: Clippings, 1984-1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - CIA: Clippings (Foreign), 1975, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - CIA Domestic Affairs, 1975-1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "CIA Off Campus - A Do-It-Yourself Handbook For Student Organizers" (Draft) Manuscript, Correspondence, Oct 18, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - CIA Publication Review Board: Policies, List of Reviewed Articles, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - CIA Base: A Computer Database on the CIA (by Ralph McGhee), 1990-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - CIA and the Church, Jul 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Center for Defense Information, Washington DC, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Central Council of Jews in Germany: Letter of Support for Agee at Hamburg University, Jan 31, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Cesio: Spanish Intelligence Service, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The Chicago Committee to Defend the Bill of Rights (Flier), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The Churchman, Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Citizens' Action Group, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Citizens for the Demilitarization of Harewood (New Zealand), Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Clippings on Publication of Interest to Agee, 1985-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "Cold War Remembered" PBS TV Series, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - The Committee for the Free World, Apr 6, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Concerned Americans Abroad (London, UK), Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Copeland, Miles; CIA Associate (Clippings), Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Council Against Communist Aggression, Washington, DC, Apr 11, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Council For Inter-American Security, Washington DC, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Counterspy" Clippings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Counterterrorism (Clippings), 1978-1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24A)
    - Covert Action Quarterly, 1994, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 24B)
    - Covert Operations Working Group, Washington DC, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Donald Freed Defense Fund (Pacific Palisades, CA), Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - European Press Agencies Adress List, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - European Intelligence Services: Clippings, Circulars, 1977-1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Eveland, Wilbur, former CIA Agent, Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Exposure of CIA Agents, 1976-1989 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - FBI and Cointelpro: Articles, 1976, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Foreign Control Watchdog, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Foreign Military Sales, Foreign Military Construction Sales and Military Assisstance Facts as of September 30, 1993" by Defense Security Assisstance Agency (DSAA) (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Free Trade Union Institute: Request to the National Endowment for Democracy Re: African-American Labor Center, Asian-American Free Labor Development, American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - "Gladio-Timewatch" Script by James Jesus Angleton, Head of CIA Counter-Intelligence 1954-1974, Apr 30, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Gladio (Operation): Italian Secret Network Anticipating the Soviet Overrunning of the West: Clippings (English, Spanish, Italian), 1990-1994 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - The Heritage Foundation: "To Restore Balance, Freedom of Information and National Security", Sep 23, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Honolulu Loan Scam Affair, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - "Injerencia - La Invasion Silenciose" - Documentary on Cuba Directed by Jose Angel Palacios), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Iran: Leak of US State Documents at the Embassy, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), Nov 1979 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Islands of the Empire": New Zealand's Military Links with the United States (Documentary) Review, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - KGB (Clipping), Dec 26 1976 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Korean Air Flight 007 Shot Down by Soviet Union: Clippings, Articles, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Lens, Sidney: Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Institute for Media analysis, New York, Apr 14, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Intelligence Identites Protection (Clippings, House Congressional Records), 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - International Covert Operations, Apr 1984 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Job Advertisements for the CIA, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Labor Advisory Committee on Foreign Assistance, Undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Labor Affairs Task Force, Sep 19, 1978-Sep 26, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Labor Unions: Bibliographies, Clippings (English, Spanish), 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Liason: France (Intelligence Services), 1974-1985 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Liason: Germany (Intelligence Services), 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Liason Great Britain (Intelligence Services), 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Liason Italy (Intelligence Services), 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation - Japanese Transaction, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Maryknoll Order, Undated (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - McGeehee, Ralph: Clippings, Correspondence (Editor of CIA Base, Author of "My 25 Years in the CIA"), 1978-1984 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - McGrady, Kevin Joseph (Affiliated with the IRA), "Written Statement After Caution), Jan 14, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - "Mike Harrington's Censure Fight: What Can't a Congressman Say?" (The Real Paper), Jul 9, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Miller, Virginia: FBI Agent, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Mind Control: Clippings, 1975-1984 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Mossad: Clippings, Articles, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - National Intelligence Study Center, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - National Security Agency: Clippings, 1966-1987 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - New Internationalist: Subscription Flier, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Nugan Hand: Australian Bank - Connected to CIA, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Nuremberg Actions (CIA): The People's Nuremberg Pledge, Undated (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - The Overseas Education Fund of the League of Women Voters of the United States, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Pacific Research and World Empire Telegraph: "Asian Labor: The American Connection", Jul-Aug, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Pacific Research and World Empire Telegram: "US Foreign Policy - a Radical Study Guide" (Vol. III, No. 3), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - People's Alliance: "Abolish the FBI CIA: End Government Repression!", Undated (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Phoenix Program: Counterinsurgency by the CIA in Vietnam, includes the transcript of the East German film "Phoenix", 1975-1983 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Project Democracy (The Democracy Program), Reagan's Initiative to Promote Democracy: Agee's Notes, Nov 30, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Project Democracy: "American Labor's Role in Promoting Free Trade Unionism and Democracy Abroad" Appendix A-H, Undated (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Project Democracy: "American Labor's Role in Promoting Free Trade Unionism and Democracy Abroad", Undated (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Project Democracy: Events Leading to the Establishment of the National Endowment for Democracy: Report to Senator Malcolm Wallop, Jul 6, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Project Democracy/National Endowment for Democracy: Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Project Democracy: Secretary George P. Shultz's Statement Before the Subcommittee on International Operations of the House Foreign Affairs Committee, Feb 23, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Reiter/innen für den Frieden (Riders for Peace), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Resistance International (International de la Resistance), Nov 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Ros, Nicolas Sirgado Ros - Cuban Double Agent, Oct 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Schevitz, Jeffrey: Accused of Espionage for Former East Germany (Includes his Indictment in German), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Security and Intelligence Fund, Washington D.C., Sept 29, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Seven Days Magazine, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Schultz/Weinberger Debate, the Use of Force in US Diplomacy, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Societe Generale de Surveillance (SGS), Control Service, Inc.: Shipments Ordered by Islamic Republic of Iran, Jan 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Solidarity (Polish Trade Union/Social Movement), 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - South African Airforce, 1st Flight of Tigershark, Sep 9, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Southern Air Transport and the CIA," Information Packet by White Rose Affinity Group Berkeley, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Steinsmith, William, MD; Sentenced for Tax Resistance: Press Release, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Student Action Union, New Jersey, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Toth, Robert C., Los Angeles Times Correspondent Arrested by KGB, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Transnational Features Service: Press Releases and Articles, Re, Labor Movements, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Turner, Stansfield (Admiral): Director, Central Intelligence Agency-Comments, Q & A, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Twentieth Century Fund: Task Force on the Future of US Intelligence Agencies, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - United States Army Intelligence Support Activity (USAISA), undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - University of Miami: CIA's "Overt" Office (Clipping), Mar 9, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - US Economy: Clippings, 1974-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - US Foreign Policy: Clippings, 1974-1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - The Vietnam Trial Support Committee, Washington D.C., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Under the Flag Documentary About Eight CIA Agents-Preview Invitation, Oct 22, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Violations of Liason Agreements: Articles, Clippings, 1965-1985 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Voter's Fair Ballot Initiative for Proportional Representation (San Diego, CA), undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Watergate: Investigation of CIA's Connection: Report to the Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities, Jul 2, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Welch, Richard: Assassinated CIA Agent-CBS 60 Minutes Segment (Includes Transcript, Correspondence), 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Willson, Brian: Vietnam Peace Activist (Clippings), 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Wolf, Louis (Editor of Covert Action Information Bulletin), 1972-1981 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Woolsey, Robert James, Jr.: Director of Central Intelligence, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 30)